<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to BrandonGiesing.com! on BrandonGiesing.com</title>
    <link>https://brandongiesing.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome to BrandonGiesing.com! on BrandonGiesing.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 15:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://brandongiesing.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BrandonGiesing.com: The &#39;Inky Abyss&#39; Update.</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/2018/02/17/brandongiesing.com-the-inky-abyss-update./</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/2018/02/17/brandongiesing.com-the-inky-abyss-update./</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the new BrandonGiesing.com! The &amp;lsquo;Inky Abyss&amp;rsquo; Update Welcome to the brand-new website! Now way faster and simplier than before!
Some things will be a bit rough around the edges while I migrate. If you see any issues, contact me on Twitter.
If you can&amp;rsquo;t find something from the old site, an Outdated copy of old Ghost site is up on GitHub just in case.
Just like last time (The Nepdate), I&amp;rsquo;m continuing the tradition of naming major updates in reference to fandoms (Hyperdimension Neptunia).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TWiT Schedule Fall 2017: My Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/10/02/twit-schedule-fall-2017-my-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 01:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/10/02/twit-schedule-fall-2017-my-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>Dear TWiT:
If you have seen things I&amp;rsquo;ve shared in the past, you might know that I&amp;rsquo;m obsessed with Technology and been critical of some of the changes you&amp;rsquo;ve made in the past. The past few years have been a bit rocky over there with various controversies, studio changes, show cancelations, etc. For a while, I tuned out of all but one show (All About Android) cause things had gotten to a point where a lot of it was just uninteresting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CosiMine | Support the site!</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/cosimine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 18:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/cosimine/</guid>
      <description>I want to keep this website (and most of what I do) availiable without really shitty ads. Below is a Crypto miner that will let you help by using a tiny bit of your CPU usage to make me some Cryptocurrency.

FAQ Is this bad for my machine? Can I adjust it to use more or less of my PCs power? Unless your machine is a potato, likely no.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here Comes The Steem Train! | Updates &amp; Stuff 5</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/08/27/here-comes-the-steem-train--updates--stuff-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 04:51:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/08/27/here-comes-the-steem-train--updates--stuff-5/</guid>
      <description>Time for more updates! This one focuses a bit less on the website for once and more on other various projects!
Steem I&amp;rsquo;m now on this blogging platform called Steem which you get paid to post. If that sounds familar, you might remember multiple platforms in the past that promised the same (Tsu, Rabadaba, etc.) but this one is quite a bit different!
Unlike those, Steem is not only a blog but a full blown platform consisting of their own Crypto Currency (think Bitcoin), a blockchain (also like Bitcoin, allows everything to be verifible and distributed), and multiple apps (some official and some unofficial) based on said Blockchain and currency:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghost 1.0, Apps, and More! | Updates &amp; Stuff 4</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/08/12/ghost-1.0-apps-and-more--updates--stuff-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 07:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/08/12/ghost-1.0-apps-and-more--updates--stuff-4/</guid>
      <description>A lot has changed since the last post but a lot of it isn&amp;rsquo;t visible so lets discuss it!
Website Updates New Server As much as I loved using NearlyFreeSpeech, there was some issues with it involving Ghost. Ghost 1.0 just came out and now requires more stuff to install which NearlyFreeSpeech doesn&amp;rsquo;t allow being a shared host.
So to upgrade to Ghost 1.0, I&amp;rsquo;ve moved over to DigitalOcean instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Love In This Timeline | Glitchtale Season 2</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/06/29/no-love-in-this-timeline--glitchtale-season-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 13:49:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/06/29/no-love-in-this-timeline--glitchtale-season-2/</guid>
      <description>For once, nobody died! I applaud you Camila for holding back this one episode! Then again, it is only Part 1 so if Part 2 has deaths I guess someone did die, in that case, NotLikeThis Camila!
CREDITS MUSIC The Undying (from the Glitchtale OST) - NyxTheShield (from Glitchtale OST)
CLIPS Glitchtale S2 E4 - Love (Part 1)
OUTRO MUSIC Energy - Michael Craig &amp;amp; Oliver Godfrey</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Casting to new heights! | Big CosiCast Update!</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/06/27/casting-to-new-heights--big-cosicast-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 14:52:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/06/27/casting-to-new-heights--big-cosicast-update/</guid>
      <description>CosiCast is getting a major overhaul with some HUGE changes!
Redefining Current Shows At the end of last year, I made some changes to CosiCast to divide my content up into Shows based on the content.
These included:
 Shorties: Short random videos covering a range of things from music edits to memes. In 60 Seconds: A topic presented at a fast pace, visual only way! No text or talking, only images, videos, and music!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More, More, More, and most importantly, MORE! | Updates &amp; Stuff 3</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/06/27/more-more-more-and-most-importantly-more--updates--stuff-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 11:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/06/27/more-more-more-and-most-importantly-more--updates--stuff-3/</guid>
      <description>Another week and more updates! This week&amp;rsquo;s focus is doing more of various things.
Support Me Page Updated If you love what I do, it would be really nice if you helped me to make more! That&amp;rsquo;s why I have a page with ways you guys can help me continue to do what I do. A lot of the options don&amp;rsquo;t even require you to have to spend money to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready, Set, DIE! | Glitchtale Season 2</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/05/30/ready-set-die--glitchtale-season-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/05/30/ready-set-die--glitchtale-season-2/</guid>
      <description>With the new episode of Glitchtale, Love Part 1, being released today, I realized I completely forgot to do my usual edit for each episode!
So for Do or Die, I decided to change things up slightly with my edit. I really tried to make it faster pace and cram more stuff in to seem more action packed. My other two edits for My Sunshine and Dust were both slower paced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Store, Secure, Speed, Splitting, and more S words! | Updates &amp; Stuff 2</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/05/29/store-secure-speed-splitting-and-more-s-words--updates--stuff-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2017 10:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/05/29/store-secure-speed-splitting-and-more-s-words--updates--stuff-2/</guid>
      <description>Another Update so soon! :O Yep, I&amp;rsquo;ve made more changes since the move to the new server so I want to make another Update post!
New Site Features and Improvements I&amp;rsquo;ve added a cool new thing to the site and also made some changes to make it even faster and more secure!
Cosi&amp;rsquo;s Commerce Store Since I talk about a lot of products, I figured I would set up an AStore with Amazon where you can buy some things I like or talk about and support me in the process!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Host, Same Site | Updates &amp; Stuff 1</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/05/22/new-host-same-site--updates--stuff-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 01:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/05/22/new-host-same-site--updates--stuff-1/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the first of a series of update posts I&amp;rsquo;ll be doing occasionally! This week, the site and email has been migrated to a new host
New Host I&amp;rsquo;ve moved the site off of Ghosted and my Email off of ProtonMail. Now I&amp;rsquo;m using NearlyFreeSpeech and Gmail. Overall this should allow me to provide the same site for way less money and have more control over it.
Why switch?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bendy Builders | Bendy and the Ink Machine</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/05/03/bendy-builders--bendy-and-the-ink-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 04:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/05/03/bendy-builders--bendy-and-the-ink-machine/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to this song a lot cause it&amp;rsquo;s so freaking catchy! So I decided to edit some cool fan animations/artwork together. I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to spend too much time so it&amp;rsquo;s not a full blown Fan Music Video but if you guys want it, let me know and maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll extend it later!
CREDITS Bendy and the Ink Machine belongs to theMeatly Games.
MUSIC Build Our Machine - DAGames</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jazzy Dragon Lolis | Miss Kobayashi&#39;s Dragon Maid</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/04/28/jazzy-dragon-lolis--miss-kobayashis-dragon-maid/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 21:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/04/28/jazzy-dragon-lolis--miss-kobayashis-dragon-maid/</guid>
      <description>First off, I want to say sorry for the severe lack of videos! I&amp;rsquo;ve either been way to busy or have no ideas when not.
I just recently started getting into this wonderful anime and you should check it out also! Here&amp;rsquo;s an edit of some of the best clips from the show so far set to an instrumental of the show&amp;rsquo;s awesome, jazzy theme song!
Also, since I have been away so long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Launch of the Casting With Cosi Show on Anchor.fm!</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/03/24/launch-of-the-casting-with-cosi-show-on-anchor.fm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 09:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/03/24/launch-of-the-casting-with-cosi-show-on-anchor.fm/</guid>
      <description>I launched a cool new variety radio show/podcast on Anchor.fm! Check it out at the show page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BrandonGiesing.com: The Nepdate!</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/01/23/brandongiesing.com-the-nepdate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 17:52:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/2017/01/23/brandongiesing.com-the-nepdate/</guid>
      <description>Funny titles aside, welcome to a new year with a new redesign for the site! Keep reading to learn about the changes or skip to the bottom for a tl;dr changelog.
What&amp;rsquo;s New Theme The theme is changed from Caffeine by Kelvin Nguyen to Mapache by GodoFredo. Both themes are good but I liked the more modern style and easier customization of Mapache.
Example: Caffeine required code editing to change Social links and logo while Mapache does it with Ghost&amp;rsquo;s simple Code injection making it easier to update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perk Tips</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/perk-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 02:49:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/perk-tips/</guid>
      <description>When people think of &amp;ldquo;Passive Video Earning Apps&amp;rdquo;, Perk is one of the biggest ones. Recently, they haven&amp;rsquo;t been the best but they are still decent enough with not as many options.
Changelog  v2: March 3rd, 2017  Add Netflix Trailers to recommended Perk TV list. Sort the apps by which ones I use more often Change Perk v2 references as v2 is the main site now Add Perk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>InstaGC Tips</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/instagc-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 00:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/instagc-tips/</guid>
      <description>InstaGC is a great site for a few simple reasons:
 They have a supportive staff! Most websites don&amp;rsquo;t seem to care about users at all but InstaGC works really hard to make sure users get the best they can. It&amp;rsquo;s in their name! Insta aka Instant! Almost everything on their site pays out instantly and you can cash out for many gift cards or PayPal instantly. Almost everything (including videos) is HTML5/Mobile compatible so there&amp;rsquo;s not as many earning problems from Flash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CosiCast 2016 Lookback</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/2016/12/11/cosicast-2016-lookback/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 05:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/2016/12/11/cosicast-2016-lookback/</guid>
      <description>From all the tragedies, YouTube&amp;rsquo;s crap, Trump, and more, this year has been one with many problems&amp;hellip; However, there&amp;rsquo;s been good things also including great new games, Scientific and Medical breakthroughs, and even more.
However, none of the above is the focus right now. Instead let&amp;rsquo;s take a moment to lookback at how I&amp;rsquo;ve improved the video content I make! This is the 2016 Lookback at CosiCast. (formally CosiTube and before that my name)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the new BrandonGiesing.com!</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/2016/09/19/welcome-to-the-new-brandongiesing.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 10:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/2016/09/19/welcome-to-the-new-brandongiesing.com/</guid>
      <description>So if you know me, I have a &amp;ldquo;habit&amp;rdquo; of constantly moving my site cause &amp;ldquo;reasons&amp;rdquo;. This time, hopefully this will be permanent now that I got great software and money to keep it alive!
Great Software: Ghost In the past I have done many different CMS, Blog, and Static services for my sites. Wordpress, Blogger, Weebly, Webs, and even Tumblr are some of those many.
Another one I used is Jekyll.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Browser Compatbility</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/browser-compatbility/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 08:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/browser-compatbility/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apps &amp; Sites | Money Routine</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/money-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/money-apps/</guid>
      <description>Previous Page:TipsNext Page:Earnings The following is a list of apps/sites I use or have used in the past divided into sections of what type of stuff you do to earn. Each one includes some basic info and tips plus some even have dedicated pages full of tips for them.
 If they are linked or include a code, it&amp;rsquo;s my referral link! Plus, they are shortened with Shorte.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CosiCast</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/cosicast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/cosicast/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the official page for CosiCast!

Shows I like to split my content into various shows to organize everything better.
Current Shows    Shows Description     Normal Videos (aka Edits) Short random videos covering a range of things from music edits to memes. (formally called Shorties and not mentioned in the thumbnail/title since this is my normal content)   Fan Music Videos (aka FMVs) Music edits based on a topic or specific fandom using a full length song.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devices | Money Routine</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/money-devices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/money-devices/</guid>
      <description>Previous Page:Introduction &amp; ChangelogNext Page: Tips To earn like this, you are gonna need devices to earn a decent amount. You can start with either old ones you have laying around or buy really inexpensive options. This page contains some tips on choosing devices and what I use myself.
Buying Devices When buying dedicated money devices, don&amp;rsquo;t just go straight for the most inexpensive ones! Yes they may be very low priced and easier to make a return of investment (ROI) on but they will likely need to be replaced more often and you would have saved in the long run by spending a tiny bit more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Earnings | Money Routine</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/money-earnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/money-earnings/</guid>
      <description>Previous Page:Apps &amp; SitesBack to Beginning This page shows what I&amp;rsquo;ve made from what I described on the past few pages. As I said on the 1st page disclaimer, your results may vary tons so don&amp;rsquo;t blame me if you don&amp;rsquo;t earn as much.
 All earnings are my own on most sites. The only sites I have active referrals on currently are InstaGC, Swagbucks, and FreeBitcoin</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get some of my best Wallpapers and help support Charity!</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/wallpaper-collection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/wallpaper-collection/</guid>
      <description>Want a new look for your device? Get some of my best original Wallpapers and help support charity in the process!
If you use Gumroad, you can pay what you want and I&amp;rsquo;ll donate 50% of the proceeds from this Collection to the EFF and Wikimedia Foundation to help keep the internet a great and informative place! If you use Coinbase, it&amp;rsquo;s a set price of $1 in Bitcoin, Litecoin, Bitcoin Cash, and Ethereum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Money Routine</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/money/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/money/</guid>
      <description>If you are wondering how I making money with devices passively running while I mostly do nothing, this page will describe what services and devices I use plus links to blog posts with tips!
 Disclaimer: I have no job because very few people want to hire an autistic teen who has weight, sight, sleep, and knee issues. So I&amp;rsquo;m here doing this all day and most likely make more than an average person would doing this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>Over the years, I have done (or contributed to) a variety of projects.
Key To not be so repetitive, here&amp;rsquo;s a key of abbreviations for what states projects are in
   Abbreviation Meaning     DISC Discontinued   CUR Current (actively working on)   HIA Hiatus (not discontinued but also not being actively worked on)   AC Actively Contributing To   NAC Not Actively Contributing To    Personal Projects Pravox Networks (DISC) / CASTchannel (HIA) .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips | Money Routine</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/money-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/money-tips/</guid>
      <description>Previous Page:DevicesNext Page: Apps &amp;Sites While a lot of these things with very little intervention or setup, there&amp;rsquo;s various ways you can maximize your earnings and keep your devices running smooth!
Device Management  Reboot and clean devices regularly to keep everything running smoothly.  On a rooted Android, Power Schedule and SD Maid can help with this. On Windows, look into making Task Scheduler Basic Tasks to do this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ways To Support Me</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/supportme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/supportme/</guid>
      <description>If you like the various projects I do (or have done in the past), a donation would be appreciated!
No money? No problem Do you want to help me but have nothing yourself? Fear not, you still can!
Money Routine One of the easiest ways is to signup for the &amp;ldquo;beermoney&amp;rdquo; services using the referral links on my Money Making Routine page and I&amp;rsquo;ll make a bit of money while you make money.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>