<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BrandonGiesing.com</title>
    <link>https://brandongiesing.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on BrandonGiesing.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://brandongiesing.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Apps &amp; Sites | Money Routine</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/money-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/money-apps/</guid>
      <description>Previous Page: Tips&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;Next Page: Earnings
The following is a list of apps/sites I use or have used in the past divided into sections of what type of stuff you do to earn. Each one includes some basic info and tips plus some even have dedicated pages full of tips for them.
If they are linked or include a code, it&#39;s my referral link! Plus, they are shortened with Shorte.st which shows an ad redirect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CosiCast</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/cosicast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/cosicast/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the official page for CosiCast!
.tg {border-collapse:collapse;border-spacing:0;border-color:#ccc;} .tg td{padding:1px 1px;overflow:hidden;word-break:normal;} .tg th{padding:1px 1px;overflow:hidden;word-break:normal;} .tg .tg-yw4l{vertical-align:top} @media screen and (max-width: 767px) {.tg {width: auto !important;}.tg col {width: auto !important;}.tg-wrap {overflow-x: auto;-webkit-overflow-scrolling: touch;}}     
Shows Current Shows  Shorties | Short random videos covering a range of things from music edits to memes. Fan Music Videos (aka FMVs) | Music edits based on a topic or specific fandom using a full length song.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devices | Money Routine</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/money-devices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/money-devices/</guid>
      <description>Previous Page: Introduction &amp;amp; Changelog&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;Next Page: Tips
To earn like this, you are gonna need devices to earn a decent amount. You can start with either old ones you have laying around or buy really inexpensive options. This page contains some tips on choosing devices and what I use myself.
Buying Devices When buying dedicated money devices, don&amp;rsquo;t just go straight for the most inexpensive ones! Yes they may be very low priced and easier to make a return of investment (ROI) on but they will likely need to be replaced more often and you would have saved in the long run by spending a tiny bit more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Earnings | Money Routine</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/money-earnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/money-earnings/</guid>
      <description>Previous Page: Apps &amp;amp; Sites&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;Back to Beginning
This page shows what I&amp;rsquo;ve made from what I described on the past few pages. As I said on the 1st page disclaimer, your results may vary tons so don&amp;rsquo;t blame me if you don&amp;rsquo;t earn as much.
All earnings are my own on most sites. The only sites I have active referrals on currently are InstaGC, Swagbucks, and FreeBitcoin
2017 Earnings Starting April 2017, I&#39;m now tracking earnings each month instead of All-Time like I was doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get some of my best Wallpapers and help support Charity!</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/wallpaper-collection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/wallpaper-collection/</guid>
      <description>Want a new look for your device? Pay what you want for some of my best original Wallpapers and help support charity in the process!
I&amp;rsquo;ll donate 50% of the proceeds from this Collection to the EFF and Wikimedia Foundation to help keep the internet a great and informative place!
 Pay What You Want on Gumroad
About The Wallpapers There are 9 total wallpapers available divided into 4 groups:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Money Routine</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/money/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/money/</guid>
      <description>If you are wondering how I making money with devices passively running while I mostly do nothing, this page will describe what services and devices I use plus links to blog posts with tips!
Disclaimer: I have no job because very few people want to hire an autistic teen who has weight, sight, sleep, and knee issues. So I&#39;m here doing this all day and most likely make more than an average person would doing this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>Over the years, I have done (or contributed to) a variety of projects.
Key To not be so repetitive, here&amp;rsquo;s a key of abbreviations for what states projects are in
   Abbreviation Meaning     DISC Discontinued   CUR Current (actively working on)   HIA Hiatus (not discontinued but also not being actively worked on)   AC Actively Contributing To   NAC Not Actively Contributing To    Personal Projects Pravox Networks (DISC) A very passionate project of mine whose goal was to make linear TV-like stations for online content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips | Money Routine</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/money-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/money-tips/</guid>
      <description>Previous Page: Devices&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;&amp;emsp;Next Page: Apps &amp;amp; Sites
While a lot of these things with very little intervention or setup, there&amp;rsquo;s various ways you can maximize your earnings and keep your devices running smooth!
Device Management  Reboot and clean devices regularly to keep everything running smoothly.  On a rooted Android, Power Schedule and SD Maid can help with this. On Windows, look into making Task Scheduler Basic Tasks to do this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ways To Support Me</title>
      <link>https://brandongiesing.com/supportme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandongiesing.com/supportme/</guid>
      <description>If you like the various projects I do (or have done in the past), a donation would be appreciated!
No money? No problem! Do you want to help me but have nothing yourself? Fear not, you still can!
Money Routine One of the easiest ways is to signup for the &amp;ldquo;beermoney&amp;rdquo; services using the referral links on my Money Making Routine page and I&amp;rsquo;ll make a bit of money while you make money.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>